{
    "name": "Japanese N4 Vocabulary", 
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "Ah", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ah\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "like that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ああ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ああ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"like that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あいだ (a space)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"間\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a space (あいだ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"間\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "間 (あいだ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a space\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あう (to match)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"合う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to match (あう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"合う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "合う (あう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to match\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "baby", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あかちゃん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あかちゃん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"baby\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あがる (to rise)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"上る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to rise (あがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"上る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "上る (あがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to rise\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あかんぼう (baby)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"赤ん坊\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "baby (あかんぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"赤ん坊\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "赤ん坊 (あかんぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"baby\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あく (to open, to become empty)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"空く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to open, to become empty (あく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"空く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "空く (あく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to open, to become empty\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to give", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あげる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あげる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to give\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あさい (shallow, superficial)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"浅い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shallow, superficial (あさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"浅い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "浅い (あさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shallow, superficial\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あじ (flavour)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "flavour (あじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "味 (あじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"flavour\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あす・あした (tomorrow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"明日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tomorrow (あす・あした)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"明日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "明日 (あす・あした)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tomorrow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あそび (play)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遊び\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "play (あそび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遊び\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遊び (あそび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"play\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あつまる (to gather)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"集る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to gather (あつまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"集る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "集る (あつまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to gather\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あつめる (to collect something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"集める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to collect something (あつめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"集める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "集める (あつめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to collect something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あやまる (to apologize)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"謝る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to apologize (あやまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"謝る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "謝る (あやまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to apologize\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あんしん (relief)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"安心\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "relief (あんしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"安心\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "安心 (あんしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"relief\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あんぜん (safety)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"安全\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "safety (あんぜん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"安全\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "安全 (あんぜん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"safety\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "such", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"あんな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あんな", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"such\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いか (less than)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"以下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "less than (いか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"以下\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "以下 (いか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"less than\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いがい (with the exception of)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"以外\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "with the exception of (いがい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"以外\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "以外 (いがい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"with the exception of\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いがく (medical science)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"医学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "medical science (いがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"医学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "医学 (いがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"medical science\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いきる (to live)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"生きる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to live (いきる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"生きる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "生きる (いきる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to live\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いけん (opinion)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"意見\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "opinion (いけん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"意見\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "意見 (いけん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"opinion\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いし (stone)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"石\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stone (いし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"石\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "石 (いし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stone\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to tease", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いじめる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いじめる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to tease\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いじょう (more than, this is all)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"以上\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "more than, this is all (いじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"以上\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "以上 (いじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"more than, this is all\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いそぐ (to hurry)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"急ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hurry (いそぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"急ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "急ぐ (いそぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hurry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いたす ((humble) to do)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"致す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) to do (いたす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"致す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "致す (いたす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) to do\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いちど (once)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一度\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "once (いちど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一度\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一度 (いちど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"once\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いっしょうけんめい (with utmost effort)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"一生懸命\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "with utmost effort (いっしょうけんめい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"一生懸命\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "一生懸命 (いっしょうけんめい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"with utmost effort\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "full", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いっぱい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いっぱい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"full\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いと (thread)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"糸\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thread (いと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"糸\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "糸 (いと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thread\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いない (within)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"以内\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "within (いない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"以内\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "以内 (いない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"within\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いなか (countryside)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"田舎\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "countryside (いなか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"田舎\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "田舎 (いなか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"countryside\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いのる (to pray)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"祈る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to pray (いのる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"祈る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "祈る (いのる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pray\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(respectful) to be, to come or to go", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"いらっしゃる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いらっしゃる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(respectful) to be, to come or to go\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うえる (to plant, to grow)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"植える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to plant, to grow (うえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"植える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "植える (うえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to plant, to grow\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うけつけ (receipt)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"受付\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "receipt (うけつけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"受付\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "受付 (うけつけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"receipt\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うける (to take a lesson or test)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"受ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to take a lesson or test (うける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"受ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "受ける (うける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to take a lesson or test\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うごく (to move)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"動く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to move (うごく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"動く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "動く (うごく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to move\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "within", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"うち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うち", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"within\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うつ (to hit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"打つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hit (うつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"打つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "打つ (うつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うつくしい (beautiful)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"美しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beautiful (うつくしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"美しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "美しい (うつくしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beautiful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うつす (to copy or photograph)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"写す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to copy or photograph (うつす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"写す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "写す (うつす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to copy or photograph\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うつる (to move house or transfer)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"移る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to move house or transfer (うつる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"移る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "移る (うつる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to move house or transfer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うで (arm)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"腕\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "arm (うで)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"腕\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "腕 (うで)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"arm\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うら (reverse side)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"裏\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reverse side (うら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"裏\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "裏 (うら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reverse side\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うりば (place where things are sold)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"売り場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "place where things are sold (うりば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"売り場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "売り場 (うりば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"place where things are sold\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(informal) yes", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"うん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(informal) yes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うんてんしゅ (driver)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"運転手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "driver (うんてんしゅ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"運転手\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "運転手 (うんてんしゅ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"driver\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えだ (branch, twig)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"枝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "branch, twig (えだ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"枝\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "枝 (えだ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"branch, twig\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えらぶ (to choose)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"選ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to choose (えらぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"選ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "選ぶ (えらぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to choose\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えんりょ・する (to be reserved, to be restrained)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遠慮\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be reserved, to be restrained (えんりょ・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遠慮\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遠慮 (えんりょ・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be reserved, to be restrained\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(respectful) to be", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おいでになる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おいでになる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(respectful) to be\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おいわい (congratulation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お祝い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "congratulation (おいわい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お祝い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お祝い (おいわい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"congratulation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "owing to, thanks to", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おかげ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おかげ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"owing to, thanks to\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "strange or funny", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おかしい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おかしい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"strange or funny\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おく (one hundred million)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"億\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "one hundred million (おく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"億\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "億 (おく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"one hundred million\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おくじょう (rooftop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"屋上\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rooftop (おくじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"屋上\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "屋上 (おくじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rooftop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おくりもの (gift)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"贈り物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gift (おくりもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"贈り物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "贈り物 (おくりもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gift\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おくる (to send)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"送る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to send (おくる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"送る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "送る (おくる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to send\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おくれる (to be late)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遅れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be late (おくれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遅れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遅れる (おくれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be late\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おこす (to wake)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"起す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to wake (おこす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"起す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "起す (おこす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wake\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おこなう (to do)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"行う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to do (おこなう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"行う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "行う (おこなう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to do\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おこる (to get angry, to be angry)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"怒る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get angry, to be angry (おこる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"怒る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "怒る (おこる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get angry, to be angry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おしいれ (closet)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"押し入れ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "closet (おしいれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"押し入れ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "押し入れ (おしいれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"closet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おじょうさん (young lady)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お嬢さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "young lady (おじょうさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お嬢さん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お嬢さん (おじょうさん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"young lady\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おたく ((polite) your house)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お宅\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(polite) your house (おたく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お宅\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お宅 (おたく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(polite) your house\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おちる (to fall or drop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"落る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to fall or drop (おちる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"落る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "落る (おちる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fall or drop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(respectful) to say", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おっしゃる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おっしゃる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(respectful) to say\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おっと (husband)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "husband (おっと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夫 (おっと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"husband\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "change from purchase, balance", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おつり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おつり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"change from purchase, balance\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おと (sound, note)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"音\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sound, note (おと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"音\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "音 (おと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sound, note\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとす (to drop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"落す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to drop (おとす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"落す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "落す (おとす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to drop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おどり (a dance)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"踊り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a dance (おどり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"踊り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "踊り (おどり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a dance\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おどる (to dance)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"踊る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to dance (おどる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"踊る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "踊る (おどる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to dance\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おどろく (to be surprised)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"驚く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be surprised (おどろく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"驚く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "驚く (おどろく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be surprised\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おまつり (festival)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お祭り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "festival (おまつり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お祭り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お祭り (おまつり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"festival\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おみまい (calling on someone who is ill, enquiry)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お見舞い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "calling on someone who is ill, enquiry (おみまい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お見舞い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お見舞い (おみまい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"calling on someone who is ill, enquiry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おみやげ (souvenir)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お土産\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "souvenir (おみやげ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お土産\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お土産 (おみやげ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"souvenir\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもいだす (to remember)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"思い出す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to remember (おもいだす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"思い出す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "思い出す (おもいだす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to remember\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもう (to think, to feel)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"思う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to think, to feel (おもう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"思う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "思う (おもう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to think, to feel\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "toy", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"おもちゃ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもちゃ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"toy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもて (the front)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"表\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the front (おもて)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"表\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "表 (おもて)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the front\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おや (parents)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"親\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "parents (おや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"親\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "親 (おや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"parents\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "およぎかた (way of swimming)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"泳ぎ方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "way of swimming (およぎかた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"泳ぎ方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "泳ぎ方 (およぎかた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"way of swimming\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おりる (to get off, to descend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get off, to descend (おりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下りる (おりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get off, to descend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おる (to break or to fold)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"折る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to break or to fold (おる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"折る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "折る (おる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to break or to fold\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おれい (expression of gratitude)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お礼\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "expression of gratitude (おれい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お礼\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お礼 (おれい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"expression of gratitude\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おれる (to break or be folded)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"折れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to break or be folded (おれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"折れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "折れる (おれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to break or be folded\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おわり (the end)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"終わり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the end (おわり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"終わり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "終わり (おわり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the end\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいがん (coast)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"海岸\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "coast (かいがん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"海岸\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "海岸 (かいがん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"coast\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいぎ (meeting)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"会議\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "meeting (かいぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"会議\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "会議 (かいぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"meeting\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいぎしつ (meeting room)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"会議室\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "meeting room (かいぎしつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"会議室\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "会議室 (かいぎしつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"meeting room\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいじょう (assembly hall or meeting place)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"会場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "assembly hall or meeting place (かいじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"会場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "会場 (かいじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"assembly hall or meeting place\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かいわ (conversation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"会話\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "conversation (かいわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"会話\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "会話 (かいわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"conversation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かえり (return)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"帰り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "return (かえり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"帰り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "帰り (かえり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"return\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かえる (to change)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"変える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to change (かえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"変える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "変える (かえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to change\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かがく (science)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"科学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "science (かがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"科学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "科学 (かがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"science\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かがみ (mirror)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"鏡\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mirror (かがみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"鏡\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鏡 (かがみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mirror\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かける (to hang something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"掛ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hang something (かける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"掛ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "掛ける (かける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hang something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かざる (to decorate)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飾る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to decorate (かざる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飾る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飾る (かざる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to decorate\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かじ (fire)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"火事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fire (かじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"火事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "火事 (かじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fire\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gas", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ガス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gas\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かたい (hard)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"堅/硬/固い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hard (かたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"堅/硬/固い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "堅/硬/固い (かたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hard\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かたち (shape)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"形\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shape (かたち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"形\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "形 (かたち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shape\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かたづける (to tidy up)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"片付ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to tidy up (かたづける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"片付ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "片付ける (かたづける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to tidy up\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かちょう (section manager)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"課長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "section manager (かちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"課長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "課長 (かちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"section manager\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かつ (to win)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"勝つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to win (かつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"勝つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "勝つ (かつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to win\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かない (housewife)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"家内\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "housewife (かない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"家内\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "家内 (かない)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"housewife\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かなしい (sad)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"悲しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sad (かなしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"悲しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "悲しい (かなしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sad\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かならず (certainly, necessarily)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"必ず\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "certainly, necessarily (かならず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"必ず\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "必ず (かならず)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"certainly, necessarily\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かねもち/おかねもち (rich man)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"お・金持ち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rich man (かねもち/おかねもち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"お・金持ち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お・金持ち (かねもち/おかねもち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rich man\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かのじょ (she, girlfriend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"彼女\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "she, girlfriend (かのじょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"彼女\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "彼女 (かのじょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"she, girlfriend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かべ (wall)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"壁\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wall (かべ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"壁\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "壁 (かべ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wall\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かみ (hair)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"髪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hair (かみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"髪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "髪 (かみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hair\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かむ (to bite, to chew)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"噛む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to bite, to chew (かむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"噛む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "噛む (かむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to bite, to chew\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かよう (to commute)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"通う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to commute (かよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"通う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "通う (かよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to commute\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かれ (he, boyfriend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"彼\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "he, boyfriend (かれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"彼\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "彼 (かれ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"he, boyfriend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かわく (to get dry)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"乾く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get dry (かわく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"乾く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "乾く (かわく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get dry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かわり (substitute, alternate)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"代わり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "substitute, alternate (かわり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"代わり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "代わり (かわり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"substitute, alternate\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かわる (to change)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"変わる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to change (かわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"変わる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "変わる (かわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to change\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かんがえる (to consider)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"考える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to consider (かんがえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"考える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "考える (かんがえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to consider\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かんけい (relationship)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"関係\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "relationship (かんけい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"関係\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "関係 (かんけい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"relationship\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かんごし (nurse)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"看護師\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nurse (かんごし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"看護師\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "看護師 (かんごし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nurse\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かんたん (simple)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"簡単\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "simple (かんたん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"簡単\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "簡単 (かんたん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"simple\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "き (spirit, mood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "spirit, mood (き)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "気 (き)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"spirit, mood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きかい (opportunity)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"機会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "opportunity (きかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"機会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "機会 (きかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"opportunity\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きけん (danger)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"危険\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "danger (きけん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"危険\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "危険 (きけん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"danger\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きこえる (to be heard)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"聞こえる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be heard (きこえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"聞こえる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "聞こえる (きこえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be heard\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きしゃ (steam train)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"汽車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "steam train (きしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"汽車\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "汽車 (きしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"steam train\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぎじゅつ (art, technology, skill)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"技術\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "art, technology, skill (ぎじゅつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"技術\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "技術 (ぎじゅつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"art, technology, skill\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きせつ (season)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"季節\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "season (きせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"季節\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "季節 (きせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"season\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きそく (regulations)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"規則\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "regulations (きそく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"規則\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "規則 (きそく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"regulations\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "surely", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"きっと\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きっと", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"surely\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きぬ (silk)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"絹\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "silk (きぬ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"絹\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "絹 (きぬ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"silk\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きびしい (strict)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"厳しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "strict (きびしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"厳しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "厳しい (きびしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"strict\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きぶん (mood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"気分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mood (きぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"気分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "気分 (きぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きまる (to be decided)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"決る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be decided (きまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"決る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "決る (きまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be decided\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きみ ((informal) You)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"君\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(informal) You (きみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"君\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "君 (きみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(informal) You\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きめる (to decide)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"決める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to decide (きめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"決める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "決める (きめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to decide\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きもち (feeling, mood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"気持ち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "feeling, mood (きもち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"気持ち\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "気持ち (きもち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"feeling, mood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きもの (kimono)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"着物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kimono (きもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"着物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "着物 (きもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kimono\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きゃく (guest, customer)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"客\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "guest, customer (きゃく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"客\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "客 (きゃく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"guest, customer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きゅう (urgent, steep)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"急\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "urgent, steep (きゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"急\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "急 (きゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"urgent, steep\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きゅうこう (speedy, express)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"急行\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "speedy, express (きゅうこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"急行\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "急行 (きゅうこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"speedy, express\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょういく (education)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"教育\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "education (きょういく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"教育\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "教育 (きょういく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"education\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょうかい (church)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"教会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "church (きょうかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"教会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "教会 (きょうかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"church\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょうそう (competition)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"競争\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "competition (きょうそう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"競争\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "競争 (きょうそう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"competition\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きょうみ (an interest)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"興味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "an interest (きょうみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"興味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "興味 (きょうみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"an interest\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きんじょ (neighbourhood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"近所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "neighbourhood (きんじょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"近所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "近所 (きんじょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"neighbourhood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぐあい (condition, health)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"具合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "condition, health (ぐあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"具合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "具合 (ぐあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"condition, health\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くうき (air, atmosphere)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"空気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "air, atmosphere (くうき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"空気\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "空気 (くうき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"air, atmosphere\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くうこう (airport)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"空港\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "airport (くうこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"空港\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "空港 (くうこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"airport\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くさ (grass)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"草\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grass (くさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"草\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "草 (くさ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grass\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くび (neck)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"首\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "neck (くび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"首\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "首 (くび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"neck\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くも (cloud)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"雲\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cloud (くも)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"雲\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "雲 (くも)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cloud\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くらべる (to compare)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"比べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to compare (くらべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"比べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "比べる (くらべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to compare\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to give", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"くれる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くれる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to give\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くれる (to get dark, to come to an end)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"暮れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get dark, to come to an end (くれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"暮れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暮れる (くれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get dark, to come to an end\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くん (suffix for familiar young male)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"君\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suffix for familiar young male (くん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"君\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "君 (くん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suffix for familiar young male\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "け (hair or fur)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"毛\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hair or fur (け)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"毛\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "毛 (け)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hair or fur\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けいざい (finance, economy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"経済\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "finance, economy (けいざい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"経済\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "経済 (けいざい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"finance, economy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けいさつ (police)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"警察\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "police (けいさつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"警察\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "警察 (けいさつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"police\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けしき (scene, landscape)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"景色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "scene, landscape (けしき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"景色\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "景色 (けしき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"scene, landscape\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けしゴム (eraser)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"消しゴム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "eraser (けしゴム)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"消しゴム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "消しゴム (けしゴム)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"eraser\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "げしゅく (lodging)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下宿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lodging (げしゅく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下宿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下宿 (げしゅく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lodging\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けっして (never)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"決して\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "never (けっして)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"決して\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "決して (けっして)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"never\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "however", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"けれど/けれども\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けれど/けれども", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"however\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "げんいん (cause, source)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"原因\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cause, source (げんいん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"原因\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "原因 (げんいん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cause, source\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to quarrel", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"けんか・する\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けんか・する", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to quarrel\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けんきゅう (research)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"研究\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "research (けんきゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"研究\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "研究 (けんきゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"research\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けんきゅうしつ (study room, laboratory)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"研究室\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "study room, laboratory (けんきゅうしつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"研究室\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "研究室 (けんきゅうしつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"study room, laboratory\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けんぶつ (sightseeing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"見物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sightseeing (けんぶつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"見物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "見物 (けんぶつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sightseeing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こ (child)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "child (こ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "子 (こ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"child\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "this way", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"こう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"this way\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうがい (outskirts)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"郊外\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "outskirts (こうがい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"郊外\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "郊外 (こうがい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"outskirts\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうぎ (lecture)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"講義\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lecture (こうぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"講義\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "講義 (こうぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lecture\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうぎょう (the manufacturing industry)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"工業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the manufacturing industry (こうぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"工業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "工業 (こうぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the manufacturing industry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうこう (high school)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"高校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "high school (こうこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"高校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "高校 (こうこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"high school\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうこうせい (high school student)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"高校生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "high school student (こうこうせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"高校生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "高校生 (こうこうせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"high school student\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうじょう/こうば (factory, plant, mill, workshop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"工場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "factory, plant, mill, workshop (こうじょう/こうば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"工場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "工場 (こうじょう/こうば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"factory, plant, mill, workshop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうちょう (headmaster)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"校長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "headmaster (こうちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"校長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "校長 (こうちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"headmaster\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうつう (traffic, transportation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"交通\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "traffic, transportation (こうつう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"交通\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "交通 (こうつう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"traffic, transportation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうどう (auditorium)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"講堂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "auditorium (こうどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"講堂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "講堂 (こうどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"auditorium\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうとうがっこう (high school)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"高等学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "high school (こうとうがっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"高等学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "高等学校 (こうとうがっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"high school\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こうむいん (civil servant, government worker)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"公務員\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "civil servant, government worker (こうむいん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"公務員\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "公務員 (こうむいん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"civil servant, government worker\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こくさい (international)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"国際\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "international (こくさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"国際\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "国際 (こくさい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"international\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こころ (heart, mind, core)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"心\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "heart, mind, core (こころ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"心\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "心 (こころ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"heart, mind, core\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごしゅじん ((honorable) your husband)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"御主人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(honorable) your husband (ごしゅじん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"御主人\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "御主人 (ごしゅじん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(honorable) your husband\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こしょう・する (to break-down)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"故障\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to break-down (こしょう・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"故障\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "故障 (こしょう・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to break-down\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごぞんじ ((respect form ) to know)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"ご存じ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(respect form ) to know (ごぞんじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ご存じ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ご存じ (ごぞんじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(respect form ) to know\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こたえ (response)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"答\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "response (こたえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"答\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "答 (こたえ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"response\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a feast", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ごちそう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごちそう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a feast\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ことり (small bird)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"小鳥\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "small bird (ことり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"小鳥\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "小鳥 (ことり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"small bird\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the other day, recently", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"このあいだ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "このあいだ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the other day, recently\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "these days, nowadays", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"このごろ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "このごろ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"these days, nowadays\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こまかい (small, fine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"細かい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "small, fine (こまかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"細かい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "細かい (こまかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"small, fine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こむ (to include)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"込む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to include (こむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"込む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "込む (こむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to include\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こめ (uncooked rice)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"米\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "uncooked rice (こめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"米\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "米 (こめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"uncooked rice\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(respectful) to see", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ごらんになる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ごらんになる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(respectful) to see\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "after this", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"これから\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "これから", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"after this\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こわい (frightening)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"怖い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "frightening (こわい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"怖い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "怖い (こわい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"frightening\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こわす (to break)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"壊す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to break (こわす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"壊す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "壊す (こわす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to break\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こわれる (to be broken)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"壊れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be broken (こわれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"壊れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "壊れる (こわれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be broken\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こんど (now, next time)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今度\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "now, next time (こんど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今度\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今度 (こんど)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"now, next time\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こんや (tonight)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"今夜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tonight (こんや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"今夜\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "今夜 (こんや)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tonight\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さいきん (latest, nowadays)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"最近\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "latest, nowadays (さいきん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"最近\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "最近 (さいきん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"latest, nowadays\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さいご (last, end)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"最後\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "last, end (さいご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"最後\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "最後 (さいご)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"last, end\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さいしょ (beginning, first)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"最初\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beginning, first (さいしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"最初\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "最初 (さいしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beginning, first\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さか (slope, hill)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"坂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "slope, hill (さか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"坂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "坂 (さか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"slope, hill\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さがす (to look for)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"探す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to look for (さがす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"探す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "探す (さがす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to look for\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さがる (to get down, to descend)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get down, to descend (さがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下る (さがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get down, to descend\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さかん (popularity, prosperous)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"盛ん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "popularity, prosperous (さかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"盛ん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "盛ん (さかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"popularity, prosperous\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さげる (to hang, to lower, to move back)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hang, to lower, to move back (さげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下げる (さげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hang, to lower, to move back\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さしあげる ((polite) to give)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"差し上げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(polite) to give (さしあげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"差し上げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "差し上げる (さしあげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(polite) to give\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "some time ago", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"さっき\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さっき", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"some time ago\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さびしい (lonely)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"寂しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lonely (さびしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"寂しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寂しい (さびしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lonely\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さらいげつ (the month after next)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"さ来月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the month after next (さらいげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"さ来月\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さ来月 (さらいげつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the month after next\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さらいしゅう (the week after next)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"さ来週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the week after next (さらいしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"さ来週\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さ来週 (さらいしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the week after next\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さわぐ (to make noise, to be excited)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"騒ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to make noise, to be excited (さわぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"騒ぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "騒ぐ (さわぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to make noise, to be excited\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さわる (to touch)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"触る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to touch (さわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"触る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "触る (さわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to touch\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さんぎょう (industry)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"産業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "industry (さんぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"産業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "産業 (さんぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"industry\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ざんねん (disappointment)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"残念\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "disappointment (ざんねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"残念\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "残念 (ざんねん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"disappointment\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "し (city)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"市\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "city (し)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"市\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "市 (し)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"city\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じ (character)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"字\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "character (じ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"字\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "字 (じ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"character\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しあい (match, game)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"試合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "match, game (しあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"試合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "試合 (しあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"match, game\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しかた (method)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"仕方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "method (しかた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"仕方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "仕方 (しかた)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"method\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しけん (examination)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"試験\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "examination (しけん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"試験\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "試験 (しけん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"examination\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じこ (accident)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"事故\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "accident (じこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"事故\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "事故 (じこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"accident\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じしん (earthquake)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"地震\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "earthquake (じしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"地震\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "地震 (じしん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"earthquake\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じだい (era)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"時代\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "era (じだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"時代\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "時代 (じだい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"era\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "したぎ (underwear)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"下着\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "underwear (したぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"下着\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "下着 (したぎ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"underwear\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "firmly, steadily", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"しっかり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しっかり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"firmly, steadily\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しっぱい (failure, mistake)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"失敗\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "failure, mistake (しっぱい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"失敗\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "失敗 (しっぱい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"failure, mistake\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じてん (dictionary)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"辞典\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dictionary (じてん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"辞典\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "辞典 (じてん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dictionary\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しなもの (goods)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"品物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "goods (しなもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"品物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "品物 (しなもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"goods\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "little while", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"しばらく\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しばらく", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"little while\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しま (island)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"島\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "island (しま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"島\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "島 (しま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"island\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しみん (citizen)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"市民\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "citizen (しみん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"市民\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "市民 (しみん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"citizen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じむしょ (office)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"事務所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "office (じむしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"事務所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "事務所 (じむしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"office\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しゃかい (society, public)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"社会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "society, public (しゃかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"社会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "社会 (しゃかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"society, public\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しゃちょう (company president)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"社長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "company president (しゃちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"社長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "社長 (しゃちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"company president\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゆう (freedom)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"自由\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "freedom (じゆう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"自由\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "自由 (じゆう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"freedom\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しゅうかん (custom, manners)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"習慣\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "custom, manners (しゅうかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"習慣\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "習慣 (しゅうかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"custom, manners\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゅうしょ (an address, a residence)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"住所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "an address, a residence (じゅうしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"住所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "住所 (じゅうしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"an address, a residence\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゅうどう (judo)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"柔道\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "judo (じゅうどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"柔道\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "柔道 (じゅうどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"judo\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じゅうぶん (enough)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"十分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "enough (じゅうぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"十分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "十分 (じゅうぶん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"enough\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しゅみ (hobby)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"趣味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hobby (しゅみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"趣味\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "趣味 (しゅみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hobby\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょうかい (introduction)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"紹介\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "introduction (しょうかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"紹介\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "紹介 (しょうかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"introduction\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょうがっこう (elementary school)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"小学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "elementary school (しょうがっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"小学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "小学校 (しょうがっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"elementary school\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょうせつ (novel)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"小説\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "novel (しょうせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"小説\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "小説 (しょうせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"novel\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょうらい (future, prospects)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"将来\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "future, prospects (しょうらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"将来\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "将来 (しょうらい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"future, prospects\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しょくりょうひん (groceries)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"食料品\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "groceries (しょくりょうひん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"食料品\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "食料品 (しょくりょうひん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"groceries\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じょせい (woman)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"女性\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "woman (じょせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"女性\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "女性 (じょせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"woman\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しらせる (to notify)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"知らせる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to notify (しらせる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"知らせる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "知らせる (しらせる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to notify\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しらべる (to investigate)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"調べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to investigate (しらべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"調べる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "調べる (しらべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to investigate\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じんこう (population)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"人口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "population (じんこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"人口\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "人口 (じんこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"population\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "じんじゃ (Shinto shrine)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"神社\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Shinto shrine (じんじゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"神社\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "神社 (じんじゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Shinto shrine\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しんせつ (kindness)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"親切\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kindness (しんせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"親切\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "親切 (しんせつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kindness\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しんぶんしゃ (newspaper company)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"新聞社\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "newspaper company (しんぶんしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"新聞社\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "新聞社 (しんぶんしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"newspaper company\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すいえい (swimming)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"水泳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "swimming (すいえい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"水泳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "水泳 (すいえい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"swimming\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すいどう (water supply)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"水道\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "water supply (すいどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"水道\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "水道 (すいどう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"water supply\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すうがく (mathematics, arithmetic)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"数学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mathematics, arithmetic (すうがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"数学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "数学 (すうがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mathematics, arithmetic\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すぎる (to exceed)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"過ぎる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to exceed (すぎる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"過ぎる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "過ぎる (すぎる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to exceed\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すごい (terrific)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"凄い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "terrific (すごい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"凄い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "凄い (すごい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"terrific\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すすむ (to make progress)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"進む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to make progress (すすむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"進む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "進む (すすむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to make progress\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "completely", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"すっかり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すっかり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"completely\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "straight, all of a sudden", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"すっと\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すっと", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"straight, all of a sudden\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すてる (to throw away)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"捨てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to throw away (すてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"捨てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "捨てる (すてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to throw away\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すな (sand)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"砂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sand (すな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"砂\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "砂 (すな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sand\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すべる (to slide, to slip)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"滑る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to slide, to slip (すべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"滑る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "滑る (すべる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to slide, to slip\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すみ (corner, nook)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"隅\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "corner, nook (すみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"隅\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "隅 (すみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"corner, nook\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すむ (to finish)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"済む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to finish (すむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"済む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "済む (すむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to finish\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pickpocket", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"すり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pickpocket\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "then", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"すると\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すると", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"then\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せいかつ・する (to live)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"生活\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to live (せいかつ・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"生活\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "生活 (せいかつ・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to live\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せいさん・する (to produce)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"生産\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to produce (せいさん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"生産\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "生産 (せいさん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to produce\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せいじ (politics, government)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"政治\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "politics, government (せいじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"政治\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "政治 (せいじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"politics, government\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せいよう (western countries)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"西洋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "western countries (せいよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"西洋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "西洋 (せいよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"western countries\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せかい (the world)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"世界\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "the world (せかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"世界\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "世界 (せかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"the world\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せき (seat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"席\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "seat (せき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"席\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "席 (せき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"seat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せつめい (explanation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"説明\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "explanation (せつめい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"説明\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "説明 (せつめい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"explanation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せなか (back of the body)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"背中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "back of the body (せなか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"背中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "背中 (せなか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"back of the body\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せん (line)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"線\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "line (せん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"線\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "線 (せん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"line\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せんそう (war)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"戦争\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "war (せんそう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"戦争\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "戦争 (せんそう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"war\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せんぱい (senior)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"先輩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "senior (せんぱい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"先輩\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "先輩 (せんぱい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"senior\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "really", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"really\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そだてる (to rear, to bring up)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"育てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to rear, to bring up (そだてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"育てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "育てる (そだてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to rear, to bring up\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そつぎょう (graduation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"卒業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "graduation (そつぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"卒業\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "卒業 (そつぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"graduation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そふ (grandfather)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"祖父\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grandfather (そふ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"祖父\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "祖父 (そふ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandfather\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そぼ (grandmother)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"祖母\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grandmother (そぼ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"祖母\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "祖母 (そぼ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandmother\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "because of that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"それで\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "それで", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"because of that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "moreover", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"それに\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "それに", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"moreover\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to that extent", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"それほど\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "それほど", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to that extent\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gradually, soon", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そろそろ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そろそろ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gradually, soon\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "that sort of", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そんな\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そんな", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"that sort of\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "so much, like that", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"そんなに\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そんなに", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"so much, like that\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいいん・する (to leave hospital)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"退院\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to leave hospital (たいいん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"退院\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "退院 (たいいん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to leave hospital\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいがくせい (university student)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大学生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "university student (だいがくせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大学生\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大学生 (だいがくせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"university student\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいじ (important, valuable, serious matter)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "important, valuable, serious matter (だいじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大事 (だいじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"important, valuable, serious matter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいたい (generally)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大体\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "generally (だいたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大体\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大体 (だいたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"generally\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "usually", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たいてい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいてい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"usually\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だいぶ (greatly)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"大分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "greatly (だいぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"大分\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "大分 (だいぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"greatly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たいふう (typhoon)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"台風\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "typhoon (たいふう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"台風\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "台風 (たいふう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"typhoon\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たおれる (to break down)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"倒れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to break down (たおれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"倒れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "倒れる (たおれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to break down\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "so, therefore", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"だから\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だから", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"so, therefore\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たしか (definite)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"確か\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "definite (たしか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"確か\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "確か (たしか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"definite\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たす (to add a number)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"足す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to add a number (たす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"足す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "足す (たす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to add a number\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たずねる (to visit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"訪ねる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to visit (たずねる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"訪ねる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "訪ねる (たずねる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to visit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たずねる (to ask)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"尋ねる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to ask (たずねる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"尋ねる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "尋ねる (たずねる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to ask\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ただしい (correct)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"正しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "correct (ただしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"正しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "正しい (ただしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"correct\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たたみ (Japanese straw mat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"畳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Japanese straw mat (たたみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"畳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "畳 (たたみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Japanese straw mat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たてる (to stand something up)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"立てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stand something up (たてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"立てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "立てる (たてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stand something up\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たてる (to build)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"建てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to build (たてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"建てる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "建てる (たてる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to build\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たとえば (for example)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"例えば\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "for example (たとえば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"例えば\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "例えば (たとえば)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"for example\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たな (shelves)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"棚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shelves (たな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"棚\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "棚 (たな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shelves\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たのしみ (joy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"楽しみ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "joy (たのしみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"楽しみ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "楽しみ (たのしみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"joy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たのしむ (to enjoy oneself)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"楽む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to enjoy oneself (たのしむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"楽む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "楽む (たのしむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to enjoy oneself\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "occasionally", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"たまに\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たまに", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"occasionally\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ため (in order to)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"為\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "in order to (ため)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"為\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "為 (ため)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"in order to\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たりる (to be enough)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"足りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be enough (たりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"足りる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "足りる (たりる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be enough\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だんせい (male)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"男性\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "male (だんせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"男性\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "男性 (だんせい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"male\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だんぼう (heating)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"暖房\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "heating (だんぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"暖房\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暖房 (だんぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"heating\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ち (blood)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"血\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "blood (ち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"血\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "血 (ち)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"blood\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to check", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"チェック・する\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チェック・する", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to check\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちから (strength, power)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"力\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "strength, power (ちから)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"力\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "力 (ちから)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"strength, power\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "not at all (used with a negative verb)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ちっとも\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちっとも", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"not at all (used with a negative verb)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suffix for familiar person", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ちゃん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゃん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suffix for familiar person\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゅうい (caution)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"注意\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "caution (ちゅうい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"注意\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "注意 (ちゅうい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"caution\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゅうがっこう (junior high school, middle school)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"中学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "junior high school, middle school (ちゅうがっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"中学校\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "中学校 (ちゅうがっこう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"junior high school, middle school\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゅうしゃ (injection)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"注射\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "injection (ちゅうしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"注射\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "注射 (ちゅうしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"injection\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちゅうしゃじょう (parking lot)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"駐車場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "parking lot (ちゅうしゃじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"駐車場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "駐車場 (ちゅうしゃじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"parking lot\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちり (geography)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"地理\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "geography (ちり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"地理\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "地理 (ちり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"geography\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つかまえる (to seize)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"捕まえる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to seize (つかまえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"捕まえる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "捕まえる (つかまえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to seize\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つく (to be attached)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"付く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be attached (つく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"付く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "付く (つく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be attached\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つける (to soak, to pickle)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"漬ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to soak, to pickle (つける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"漬ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "漬ける (つける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to soak, to pickle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つごう (circumstances, convenience)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"都合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "circumstances, convenience (つごう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"都合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "都合 (つごう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"circumstances, convenience\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つたえる (to report)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"伝える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to report (つたえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"伝える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "伝える (つたえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to report\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つづく (to be continued)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"続く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be continued (つづく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"続く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "続く (つづく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be continued\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つづける (to continue)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"続ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to continue (つづける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"続ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "続ける (つづける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to continue\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つつむ (to wrap)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"包む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to wrap (つつむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"包む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "包む (つつむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wrap\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つま (my wife)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"妻\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "my wife (つま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"妻\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "妻 (つま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"my wife\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "intention", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"つもり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つもり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"intention\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つる (to fish)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"釣る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to fish (つる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"釣る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "釣る (つる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fish\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ていねい (polite)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"丁寧\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "polite (ていねい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"丁寧\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "丁寧 (ていねい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"polite\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てきとう (suitability)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"適当\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suitability (てきとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"適当\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "適当 (てきとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suitability\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てつだう (to assist)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"手伝う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to assist (てつだう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"手伝う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "手伝う (てつだう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to assist\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てぶくろ (glove)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"手袋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "glove (てぶくろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"手袋\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "手袋 (てぶくろ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"glove\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てら (temple)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"寺\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "temple (てら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"寺\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寺 (てら)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"temple\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てん (point, dot)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"点\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "point, dot (てん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"点\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "点 (てん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"point, dot\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てんいん (shop assistant)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"店員\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shop assistant (てんいん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"店員\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "店員 (てんいん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shop assistant\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てんきよほう (weather forecast)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"天気予報\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "weather forecast (てんきよほう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"天気予報\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "天気予報 (てんきよほう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"weather forecast\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でんとう (electric light)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"電灯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "electric light (でんとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"電灯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "電灯 (でんとう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"electric light\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "でんぽう (telegram)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"電報\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "telegram (でんぽう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"電報\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "電報 (でんぽう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"telegram\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てんらんかい (exhibition)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"展覧会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "exhibition (てんらんかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"展覧会\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "展覧会 (てんらんかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"exhibition\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と (metropolitan)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"都\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "metropolitan (と)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"都\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "都 (と)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"metropolitan\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どうぐ (tool, means)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"道具\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tool, means (どうぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"道具\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "道具 (どうぐ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tool, means\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "finally, after all", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"とうとう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とうとう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"finally, after all\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どうぶつえん (zoo)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"動物園\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "zoo (どうぶつえん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"動物園\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "動物園 (どうぶつえん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"zoo\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とおく (distant)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"遠く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "distant (とおく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"遠く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遠く (とおく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"distant\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とおる (to go through)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"通る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go through (とおる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"通る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "通る (とおる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go through\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とくに (particularly, especially)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"特に\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "particularly, especially (とくに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"特に\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "特に (とくに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"particularly, especially\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とくべつ (special)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"特別\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "special (とくべつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"特別\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "特別 (とくべつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"special\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "barber", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"とこや\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とこや", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"barber\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とちゅう (on the way)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"途中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "on the way (とちゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"途中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "途中 (とちゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"on the way\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とっきゅう (limited express train (faster than an express train))", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"特急\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "limited express train (faster than an express train) (とっきゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"特急\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "特急 (とっきゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"limited express train (faster than an express train)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とどける (to send, to deliver, to report)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"届ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to send, to deliver, to report (とどける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"届ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "届ける (とどける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to send, to deliver, to report\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とまる (to lodge at)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"泊まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to lodge at (とまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"泊まる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "泊まる (とまる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to lodge at\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とめる (to stop something)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"止める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stop something (とめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"止める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "止める (とめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stop something\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とりかえる (to exchange)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"取り替える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to exchange (とりかえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"取り替える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "取り替える (とりかえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to exchange\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どろぼう (thief)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"泥棒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thief (どろぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"泥棒\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "泥棒 (どろぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thief\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "more and more", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"どんどん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "どんどん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"more and more\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なおす (to fix, to repair)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"直す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to fix, to repair (なおす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"直す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "直す (なおす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fix, to repair\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なおる (to be fixed, to be repaired)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"直る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be fixed, to be repaired (なおる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"直る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "直る (なおる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be fixed, to be repaired\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なおる (to be cured, to heal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"治る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be cured, to heal (なおる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"治る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "治る (なおる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be cured, to heal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なく (to weep)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"泣く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to weep (なく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"泣く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "泣く (なく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to weep\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なくなる (to disappear, to get lost)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"無くなる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to disappear, to get lost (なくなる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"無くなる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "無くなる (なくなる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to disappear, to get lost\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なくなる (to die)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"亡くなる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to die (なくなる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"亡くなる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "亡くなる (なくなる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to die\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なげる (to throw or cast away)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"投げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to throw or cast away (なげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"投げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "投げる (なげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to throw or cast away\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(respectful) to do", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"なさる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なさる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(respectful) to do\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なる (to sound)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"鳴る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to sound (なる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"鳴る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鳴る (なる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sound\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "as much as possible", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"なるべく\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なるべく", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"as much as possible\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "now I understand", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"なるほど\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なるほど", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"now I understand\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なれる (to grow accustomed to)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"慣れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to grow accustomed to (なれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"慣れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "慣れる (なれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to grow accustomed to\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にがい (bitter)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"苦い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bitter (にがい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"苦い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "苦い (にがい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bitter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にかいだて (two storied)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"二階建て\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "two storied (にかいだて)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"二階建て\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "二階建て (にかいだて)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"two storied\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にげる (to escape)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"逃げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to escape (にげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"逃げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "逃げる (にげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to escape\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にっき (journal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"日記\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "journal (にっき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"日記\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "日記 (にっき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"journal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にゅういん・する (to hospitalise, hospitalisation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"入院\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to hospitalise, hospitalisation (にゅういん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"入院\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "入院 (にゅういん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hospitalise, hospitalisation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にゅうがく・する (to enter school or university)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"入学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to enter school or university (にゅうがく・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"入学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "入学 (にゅうがく・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to enter school or university\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にる (to be similar)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"似る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be similar (にる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"似る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "似る (にる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be similar\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "にんぎょう (doll, figure)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"人形\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "doll, figure (にんぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"人形\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "人形 (にんぎょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"doll, figure\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬすむ (to steal)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"盗む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to steal (ぬすむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"盗む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "盗む (ぬすむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to steal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬる (to paint, to colour, to plaster)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"塗る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to paint, to colour, to plaster (ぬる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"塗る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "塗る (ぬる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to paint, to colour, to plaster\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get wet", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ぬれる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬれる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get wet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "price", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ねだん\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねだん", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"price\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねつ (fever)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"熱\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fever (ねつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"熱\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "熱 (ねつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fever\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねぼう (sleeping in late)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"寝坊\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sleeping in late (ねぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"寝坊\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寝坊 (ねぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sleeping in late\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねむい (sleepy)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"眠い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sleepy (ねむい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"眠い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "眠い (ねむい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sleepy\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねむる (to sleep)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"眠る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to sleep (ねむる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"眠る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "眠る (ねむる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sleep\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のこる (to remain)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"残る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to remain (のこる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"残る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "残る (のこる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to remain\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のりかえる (to change between buses or trains)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"乗り換える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to change between buses or trains (のりかえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"乗り換える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "乗り換える (のりかえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to change between buses or trains\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のりもの (vehicle)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"乗り物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "vehicle (のりもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"乗り物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "乗り物 (のりもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"vehicle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "は (leaf)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"葉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "leaf (は)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"葉\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "葉 (は)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"leaf\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばあい (situation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"場合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "situation (ばあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"場合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "場合 (ばあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"situation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばい (double)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"倍\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "double (ばい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"倍\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "倍 (ばい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"double\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はいけん・する ((humble) to look at)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"拝見\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) to look at (はいけん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"拝見\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "拝見 (はいけん・する)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) to look at\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はいしゃ (dentist)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"歯医者\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dentist (はいしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"歯医者\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歯医者 (はいしゃ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dentist\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はこぶ (to transport)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"運ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to transport (はこぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"運ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "運ぶ (はこぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to transport\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はじめる (to begin)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"始める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to begin (はじめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"始める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "始める (はじめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to begin\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばしょ (location)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"場所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "location (ばしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"場所\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "場所 (ばしょ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"location\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "it should be so", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"はず\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はず", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"it should be so\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はずかしい (embarrassed)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"恥ずかしい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "embarrassed (はずかしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"恥ずかしい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "恥ずかしい (はずかしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"embarrassed\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はつおん (pronunciation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"発音\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pronunciation (はつおん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"発音\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "発音 (はつおん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pronunciation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "clearly", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"はっきり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はっきり", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"clearly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はなみ (cherry-blossom viewing)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"花見\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cherry-blossom viewing (はなみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"花見\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "花見 (はなみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cherry-blossom viewing\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はやし (woods, forester)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"林\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "woods, forester (はやし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"林\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "林 (はやし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"woods, forester\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はらう (to pay)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"払う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to pay (はらう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"払う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "払う (はらう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pay\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ばんぐみ (television or radio program)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"番組\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "television or radio program (ばんぐみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"番組\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "番組 (ばんぐみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"television or radio program\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はんたい (opposition)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"反対\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "opposition (はんたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"反対\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "反対 (はんたい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"opposition\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひ (day, sun)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "day, sun (ひ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"日\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "日 (ひ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"day, sun\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひ (fire)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"火\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fire (ひ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"火\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "火 (ひ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fire\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひえる (to grow cold)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"冷える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to grow cold (ひえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"冷える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "冷える (ひえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to grow cold\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひかり (light)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"光\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "light (ひかり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"光\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "光 (ひかり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"light\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひかる (to shine, to glitter)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"光る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to shine, to glitter (ひかる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"光る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "光る (ひかる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to shine, to glitter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひきだし (drawer, drawing out)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"引き出し\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "drawer, drawing out (ひきだし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"引き出し\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "引き出し (ひきだし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"drawer, drawing out\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to withdraw", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ひきだす\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひきだす", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to withdraw\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beard", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ひげ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひげ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beard\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひこうじょう (airport)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"飛行場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "airport (ひこうじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"飛行場\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飛行場 (ひこうじょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"airport\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひさしぶり (after a long time)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"久しぶり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "after a long time (ひさしぶり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"久しぶり\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "久しぶり (ひさしぶり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"after a long time\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "びじゅつかん (art gallery)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"美術館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "art gallery (びじゅつかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"美術館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "美術館 (びじゅつかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"art gallery\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひじょうに (extremely)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"非常に\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "extremely (ひじょうに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"非常に\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "非常に (ひじょうに)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"extremely\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひっこす (to move house)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"引っ越す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to move house (ひっこす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"引っ越す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "引っ越す (ひっこす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to move house\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひつよう (necessary)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"必要\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "necessary (ひつよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"必要\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "必要 (ひつよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"necessary\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "awful", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ひどい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひどい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"awful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひらく (to open an event)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"開く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to open an event (ひらく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"開く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "開く (ひらく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to open an event\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひるま (daytime, during the day)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昼間\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "daytime, during the day (ひるま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昼間\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昼間 (ひるま)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"daytime, during the day\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひるやすみ (noon break)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昼休み\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "noon break (ひるやすみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昼休み\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昼休み (ひるやすみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"noon break\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひろう (to pick up, to gather)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"拾う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to pick up, to gather (ひろう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"拾う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "拾う (ひろう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pick up, to gather\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふえる (to increase)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"増える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to increase (ふえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"増える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "増える (ふえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to increase\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふかい (deep)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"深い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "deep (ふかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"深い\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "深い (ふかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"deep\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふくざつ (complexity, complication)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"複雑\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "complexity, complication (ふくざつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"複雑\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "複雑 (ふくざつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"complexity, complication\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふくしゅう (revision)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"復習\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "revision (ふくしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"復習\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "復習 (ふくしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"revision\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶちょう (head of a section)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"部長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "head of a section (ぶちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"部長\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "部長 (ぶちょう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"head of a section\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふつう (usually, or a train that stops at every station)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"普通\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "usually, or a train that stops at every station (ふつう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"普通\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "普通 (ふつう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"usually, or a train that stops at every station\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grapes", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ぶどう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶどう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grapes\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふとる (to become fat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"太る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to become fat (ふとる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"太る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "太る (ふとる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to become fat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふとん (Japanese bedding, futon)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"布団\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Japanese bedding, futon (ふとん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"布団\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "布団 (ふとん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Japanese bedding, futon\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふね (ship)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"舟\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ship (ふね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"舟\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "舟 (ふね)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ship\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふべん (inconvenience)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"不便\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "inconvenience (ふべん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"不便\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "不便 (ふべん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"inconvenience\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふむ (to step on)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"踏む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to step on (ふむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"踏む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "踏む (ふむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to step on\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふりだす (to start to rain)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"降り出す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to start to rain (ふりだす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"降り出す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "降り出す (ふりだす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to start to rain\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶんか (culture)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"文化\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "culture (ぶんか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"文化\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "文化 (ぶんか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"culture\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶんがく (literature)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"文学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "literature (ぶんがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"文学\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "文学 (ぶんがく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"literature\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぶんぽう (grammar)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"文法\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grammar (ぶんぽう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"文法\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "文法 (ぶんぽう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grammar\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "べつ (different)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"別\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "different (べつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"別\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "別 (べつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"different\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "へん (strange)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"変\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "strange (へん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"変\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "変 (へん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"strange\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "へんじ (reply)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"返事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reply (へんじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"返事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "返事 (へんじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reply\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぼうえき (trade)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"貿易\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "trade (ぼうえき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"貿易\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "貿易 (ぼうえき)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"trade\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほうりつ (law)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"法律\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "law (ほうりつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"法律\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "法律 (ほうりつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"law\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぼく (I (used by males))", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"僕\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "I (used by males) (ぼく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"僕\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "僕 (ぼく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"I (used by males)\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほし (star)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"星\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "star (ほし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"星\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "星 (ほし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"star\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mostly", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ほとんど\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほとんど", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mostly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to praise", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ほめる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほめる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to praise\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほんやく (translation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"翻訳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "translation (ほんやく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"翻訳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "翻訳 (ほんやく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"translation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まいる ((humble) to go, to come)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"参る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) to go, to come (まいる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"参る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "参る (まいる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) to go, to come\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まける (to lose)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"負ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to lose (まける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"負ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "負ける (まける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to lose\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "or, otherwise", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"または\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "または", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"or, otherwise\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まちがえる (to make a mistake)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"間違える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to make a mistake (まちがえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"間違える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "間違える (まちがえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to make a mistake\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まにあう (to be in time for)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"間に合う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be in time for (まにあう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"間に合う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "間に合う (まにあう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be in time for\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まわり (surroundings)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"周り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "surroundings (まわり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"周り\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "周り (まわり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"surroundings\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まわる (to go around)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"回る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go around (まわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"回る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "回る (まわる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go around\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まんが (comic)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"漫画\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "comic (まんが)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"漫画\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "漫画 (まんが)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"comic\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まんなか (middle)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"真中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "middle (まんなか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"真中\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "真中 (まんなか)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"middle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みえる (to be in sight)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"見える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be in sight (みえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"見える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "見える (みえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be in sight\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みずうみ (lake)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"湖\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lake (みずうみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"湖\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "湖 (みずうみ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lake\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みそ (miso, soybean paste)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"味噌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "miso, soybean paste (みそ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"味噌\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "味噌 (みそ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"miso, soybean paste\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みつかる (to be discovered)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"見つかる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be discovered (みつかる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"見つかる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "見つかる (みつかる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be discovered\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みつける (to discover)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"見つける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to discover (みつける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"見つける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "見つける (みつける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to discover\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みな (everybody)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"皆\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "everybody (みな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"皆\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "皆 (みな)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"everybody\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みなと (harbour)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"港\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "harbour (みなと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"港\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "港 (みなと)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"harbour\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むかう (to face)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"向かう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to face (むかう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"向かう\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "向かう (むかう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to face\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むかえる (to go out to meet)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"迎える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to go out to meet (むかえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"迎える\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "迎える (むかえる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go out to meet\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むかし (old times, old days, long ago, formerly)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"昔\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "old times, old days, long ago, formerly (むかし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"昔\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昔 (むかし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"old times, old days, long ago, formerly\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むし (insect)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"虫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "insect (むし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"虫\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "虫 (むし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"insect\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むすこ ((humble) son)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"息子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) son (むすこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"息子\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "息子 (むすこ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) son\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むすめ ((humble) daughter)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"娘\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) daughter (むすめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"娘\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "娘 (むすめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) daughter\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むり (impossible)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"無理\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "impossible (むり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"無理\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "無理 (むり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"impossible\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "めしあがる ((polite) to eat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"召し上がる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(polite) to eat (めしあがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"召し上がる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "召し上がる (めしあがる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(polite) to eat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "めずらしい (rare)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"珍しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rare (めずらしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"珍しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "珍しい (めずらしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rare\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もうしあげる ((humble) to say, to tell)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"申し上げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) to say, to tell (もうしあげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"申し上げる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "申し上げる (もうしあげる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) to say, to tell\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もうす ((humble) to be called, to say)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"申す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(humble) to be called, to say (もうす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"申す\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "申す (もうす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"(humble) to be called, to say\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "soon", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"もうすぐ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もうすぐ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"soon\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "if", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"もし\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もし", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"if\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もどる (to turn back)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"戻る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to turn back (もどる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"戻る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "戻る (もどる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to turn back\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もめん (cotton)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"木綿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cotton (もめん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"木綿\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "木綿 (もめん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cotton\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もり (forest)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"森\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "forest (もり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"森\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "森 (もり)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"forest\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やく (to bake, to grill)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"焼く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to bake, to grill (やく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"焼く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "焼く (やく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to bake, to grill\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やくそく (promise)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"約束\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "promise (やくそく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"約束\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "約束 (やくそく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"promise\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やくにたつ (to be helpful)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"役に立つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be helpful (やくにたつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"役に立つ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "役に立つ (やくにたつ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be helpful\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やける (to burn, to be roasted)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"焼ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to burn, to be roasted (やける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"焼ける\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "焼ける (やける)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to burn, to be roasted\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やさしい (kind)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"優しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kind (やさしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"優しい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "優しい (やさしい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kind\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やせる (to become thin)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"痩せる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to become thin (やせる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"痩せる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "痩せる (やせる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to become thin\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "at last", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"やっと\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やっと", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"at last\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やむ (to stop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"止む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stop (やむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"止む\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "止む (やむ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やめる (to stop)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"止める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to stop (やめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"止める\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "止める (やめる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stop\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やわらかい (soft)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"柔らかい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "soft (やわらかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"柔らかい\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "柔らかい (やわらかい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"soft\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆ (hot water)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"湯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hot water (ゆ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"湯\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "湯 (ゆ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hot water\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆび (finger)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"指\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "finger (ゆび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"指\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "指 (ゆび)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"finger\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆびわ (a ring)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"指輪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a ring (ゆびわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"指輪\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "指輪 (ゆびわ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a ring\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆめ (dream)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"夢\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dream (ゆめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"夢\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夢 (ゆめ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dream\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆれる (to shake, to sway)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"揺れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to shake, to sway (ゆれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"揺れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "揺れる (ゆれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to shake, to sway\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よう (use)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"用\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "use (よう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"用\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "用 (よう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"use\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ようい (preparation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"用意\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "preparation (ようい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"用意\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "用意 (ようい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"preparation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ようじ (things to do)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"用事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "things to do (ようじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"用事\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "用事 (ようじ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"things to do\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よごれる (to get dirty)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"汚れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to get dirty (よごれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"汚れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "汚れる (よごれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get dirty\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よしゅう (preparation for a lesson)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"予習\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "preparation for a lesson (よしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"予習\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "予習 (よしゅう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"preparation for a lesson\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よてい (arrangement)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"予定\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "arrangement (よてい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"予定\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "予定 (よてい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"arrangement\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よやく (reservation)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"予約\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reservation (よやく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"予約\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "予約 (よやく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reservation\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よる (to visit)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"寄る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to visit (よる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"寄る\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寄る (よる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to visit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よろこぶ (to be delighted)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"喜ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to be delighted (よろこぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"喜ぶ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "喜ぶ (よろこぶ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be delighted\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りゆう (reason)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"理由\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reason (りゆう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"理由\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "理由 (りゆう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reason\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りよう (utilization)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"利用\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "utilization (りよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"利用\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "利用 (りよう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"utilization\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りょうほう (both sides)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"両方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "both sides (りょうほう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"両方\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "両方 (りょうほう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"both sides\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "りょかん (Japanese hotel)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"旅館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Japanese hotel (りょかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"旅館\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "旅館 (りょかん)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Japanese hotel\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "るす (absence)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"留守\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "absence (るす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"留守\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "留守 (るす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"absence\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "れいぼう (air conditioning)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"冷房\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "air conditioning (れいぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"冷房\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "冷房 (れいぼう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"air conditioning\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "れきし (history)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"歴史\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "history (れきし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"歴史\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歴史 (れきし)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"history\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "れんらく (contact)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"連絡\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "contact (れんらく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"連絡\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "連絡 (れんらく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"contact\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わかす (to boil, to heat)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"沸かす\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to boil, to heat (わかす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"沸かす\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "沸かす (わかす)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to boil, to heat\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わかれる (to separate)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"別れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to separate (わかれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"別れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "別れる (わかれる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to separate\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わく (to boil, to grow hot, to get excited)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"沸く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to boil, to grow hot, to get excited (わく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"沸く\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "沸く (わく)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to boil, to grow hot, to get excited\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わけ (meaning, reason)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"訳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "meaning, reason (わけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"訳\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "訳 (わけ)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"meaning, reason\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わすれもの (lost article)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"忘れ物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lost article (わすれもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"忘れ物\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "忘れ物 (わすれもの)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lost article\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わらう (to laugh, to smile)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"笑う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to laugh, to smile (わらう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"笑う\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "笑う (わらう)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to laugh, to smile\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わりあい (rate, ratio, percentage)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"割合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rate, ratio, percentage (わりあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"割合\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "割合 (わりあい)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rate, ratio, percentage\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "われる (to break)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"割れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to break (われる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"割れる\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "割れる (われる)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to break\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "accessory", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アクセサリー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アクセサリー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"accessory\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Asia", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アジア\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アジア", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Asia\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "announcer", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アナウンサー\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アナウンサー", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"announcer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Africa", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アフリカ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アフリカ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Africa\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "America", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アメリカ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アメリカ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"America\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "alcohol", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アルコール\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アルコール", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"alcohol\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "part-time job", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"アルバイト\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アルバイト", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"part-time job\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "escalator", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"エスカレーター\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エスカレーター", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"escalator\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "motorcycle", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"オートバイ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "オートバイ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"motorcycle\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "curtain", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"カーテン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カーテン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"curtain\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gas", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ガス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gas\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "petrol", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ガソリン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガソリン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"petrol\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "petrol station", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ガソリンスタンド\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガソリンスタンド", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"petrol station\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "a glass pane", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ガラス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガラス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"a glass pane\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cake", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ケーキ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケーキ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cake\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けしゴム (eraser, rubber)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the pronunciation of \"消しゴム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "eraser, rubber (けしゴム)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"消しゴム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "消しゴム (けしゴム)", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"eraser, rubber\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "concert", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"コンサート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コンサート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"concert\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "computer", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"コンピューター\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コンピューター", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"computer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "salad", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"サラダ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サラダ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"salad\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sandal", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"サンダル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サンダル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sandal\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sandwich", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"サンドイッチ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サンドイッチ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sandwich\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "jam", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ジャム\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジャム", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"jam\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suit", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スーツ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スーツ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suit\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suitcase", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スーツケース\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スーツケース", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suitcase\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "screen", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"スクリーン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スクリーン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"screen\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "steak", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ステーキ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ステーキ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"steak\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stereo", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ステレオ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ステレオ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stereo\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "soft", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ソフト\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソフト", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"soft\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "type, style", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"タイプ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タイプ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"type, style\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to check", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"チェック・する\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チェック・する", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"to check\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "text, text book", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テキスト\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テキスト", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"text, text book\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tennis", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"テニス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テニス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tennis\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "part time", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"パート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "パート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"part time\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "personal computer", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"パソコン\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "パソコン", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"personal computer\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "handbag", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ハンドバッグ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハンドバッグ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"handbag\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "piano", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ピアノ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ピアノ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"piano\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "building or bill", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ビル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ビル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"building or bill\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fax", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ファックス\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ファックス", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fax\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "present", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"プレゼント\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "プレゼント", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"present\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bell", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ベル\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ベル", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bell\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "register", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"レジ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レジ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"register\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "report", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"レポート/リポート\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レポート/リポート", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"report\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "word processor", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ワープロ\"?", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ワープロ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "Given the definition \"word processor\", what is the word?", 
            "tried": 0
        }
    ]
}